[
  { "question": "1 → ?", "answer": "uno" },
  { "question": "2 → ?", "answer": "dos" },
  { "question": "3 → ?", "answer": "tres" },
  { "question": "4 → ?", "answer": "cuatro" },
  { "question": "5 → ?", "answer": "cinco" },
  { "question": "6 → ?", "answer": "seis" },
  { "question": "7 → ?", "answer": "siete" },
  { "question": "8 → ?", "answer": "ocho" },
  { "question": "9 → ?", "answer": "nueve" },
  { "question": "10 → ?", "answer": "diez" }
]
